[
  {
    "Question": "Write the correct word (can't, could, can't, couldn't). എനിക്ക് ഉറങ്ങാനേ പറ്റിയില്ല. I ___  sleep at all",
    "Answer": "couldn't"
  },
  {
    "Question": "അവൾക്കിപ്പോൾ പരീക്ഷ കഴിഞ്ഞിരിക്കണം. How to say this in English? She _____ finished the exams by now",
    "Answers": ["should have", "should've"]
  },
  {
    "Question": "Choose the correct word: (for, to , buy). I went to the shop __ some sugar",
    "Answer": "for"
  },
  {
    "Question": "ഞാൻ എത്തിയപ്പോഴേക്കും അവർ പോയിരുന്നു. How do you say this in English?",
    "Answers":["They had left when I arrived", "When I arrived, they had left"]
  },
  {
    "Question": "Choose the correct word(s): (is, was, has been, is been).  She __ crying since morning",
    "Answer": "has been"
  },
  {
    "Question": "നിനക്ക് പോകാമായിരുന്നു. How to say this in English?",
    "Answers": ["You could have gone", "You could've gone"]
  },
  {
    "Question": " നമ്മൾ പോകണം. We ___ go. Choose the correct option (could, should, would",
    "Answer":"should"
  },
  {
    "Question": "ഞാൻ ദിവസേന വ്യായാമം ചെയ്തിരുന്നു. Fill in the correct word(s) I ___ exercise regularly",
    "Answer":"used to"},
  {
    "Question": "അവൾക്ക് ഇന്നലെ വരാൻ പറ്റിയില്ല. She ___ come yesterday. Choose the right word(s) (will not, should not, may not, could not)",
    "Answer":"could not"
  },
  {
    "Question": " This is a bad book. That book is ____ (ആ പുസ്തകം അതിലും മോശമാണ്)",
    "Answer":"worse"
  },
  {
    "Question": "ഞാൻ അധികം കഴിക്കാൻ പാടില്ലായിരുന്നു? Write the correct option (shouldn't, couldn't, shouldn't have, couldn't have) I ____ eaten to much",
    "Answer": "shouldn't have"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Change to Reported Speech) Ali:\"I am tired\"",
    "Answer":"Ali said that he was tired"
  },
  {
    "Question": "Choose the correct word(s) (should be cooking, should be cooked, should be cook). This rice ___ for 40 to 50 minutes.",
    "Answer":"the"
  },
  {
    "Question": "How do you say this in English? ഞാൻ എന്റെ കാർ നന്നാക്കിപ്പിച്ചു.",
    "Answers":["I got my car repaired", "I had my car repaired"]
  }
]

